WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
Huh? Uh... Excuse me...
Return of the
Morning Mist
My mother and my father...
They didn't have to die.
Because I didn't have strength,
the whole clan was destroyed.
Everyone was killed...
Damn it...
Morning training is over!
Once I've eaten breakfast
I'll get back to rigorous training!
Old man...
Konohamaru...
Yo! Konohamaru.
Naruto nii-chan.
Have you already resumed studies
at the academy?
N-No, not yet.
The school buildings are damaged,
so we're all repairing them.
Is that so?
How about you, Naruto nii-chan?
You're already training?
Sort of.
Wh-What?
What is it?
N-No, it's nothing...
— Hey um...!
So what is it...?
You too, nii-chan, what is it?
Nothing... really...
I don't feel lonely.
Huh?
There's no time to be feeling lonely.
Everyone is working really hard
to rebuild the village right now.
Konohamaru...
Right now, I must work for
the village even just a little bit.
So nii-chan, you work hard
at your training too.
If you don't,
I'll become Hokage before you.
Fool, I will absolutely become Hokage.
Besides... you have to graduate
from the Academy first.
Oh, that's right...
Oh, here it is.
Here, it's for you.
A free ramen ticket from Ichiraku...
Is it okay?
I already have one,
so I'm giving one to you.
Thank you, Naruto nii-chan.
Oh! Konohamaru-chan.
Good morning.
I'm going to go.
We'll work hard again today.
— Yep!
Today we're fixing the blackboards.
I brought paint.
Well! Once I've eaten ramen at Ichiraku,
I'll continue training.
This is it.
Th-This is...
A lot of time has passed since the death.
It's probably before
the Chunin Exam began.
I see, so that's it...
That Orochimaru!
After the murder of Kazekage-sama,
Orochimaru... or someone
like Kabuto played Kazekage-sama...
How thoughtless we were...
That damn Sarutobi...
Well, it's not that easy.
The one who was your opponent
was the renowned Hokage,
deemed to be strongest of
all five great nations.
However... you've done well.
Two out of the five Kage...
Stop...
Stop giving me words of sympathy.
I will kill you!
Of course, I didn't mean to...
It's true that we didn't succeed
in bringing the village down...
On the other hand, another objective
of this plan, Uchiha Sasuke...
Your leash is now on him.
In exchange for these arms
and all of my Jutsu...
If we could have gotten our hands
on that Uchiha Itachi from the beginning,
it wouldn't have been a problem.
However that's a dream that
can no longer come true.
He is stronger than I am.
That is why... I pulled myself out
from that organization...
Kakashi, huh?
What does he want?
Breakfast, breakfast!
Wait for me, my ramen.
Do you already know
his whereabouts?
Yes.
In that case, it will be easy...
Let's go.
Here it comes, here it comes.
Oh goodie, it's just like I thought.
Hidden Leaf Village...
has a high average score.
You're still doing such
a ridiculous thing?
Well yes, this is my research.
Old Man Homura and Koharu-sensei, huh?
I wonder what you advisers
want from me.
Surely, you know...
without our telling you, don't you?
You don't have to make
such scary faces.
I heard that the talks with Sand Village
have been settled without problems.
The Hidden Village in the Sand
announced that
everything was Orochimaru's handiwork.
In addition, at the moment of their
complete surrender to us, the Leaf Village,
that wasn't a very important issue
any more.
Leaf Village has no choice but
to accept their surrender and proposition
in order to restore national power.
However, the current strength of
Leaf Village has dropped drastically.
Under these conditions,
our top priority must be to prepare
for any unpredicted crisis.
We don't know when any of
the neighboring nations
will come out in a bold move.
Therefore, we've decided that until
the village gets its strength back,
we should assemble the top few men
from each troop,
and form an emergency
executive committee to handle this.
But first...
we need a strong, trustworthy leader.
You can find the seeds of trouble
rolling around everywhere these days.
It's not just Orochimaru.
You didn't have to go through
the trouble of informing me that.
Well... I'll continue gathering materials.
I'm going to tell you the basic plan.
We need the Fifth Hokage right away.
And yesterday at an emergency meeting
with the feudal lord of the Land of Fire,
we decided
it would be you, Jiraiya.
I'm sorry, it's not my nature.
It has been decided.
Besides, if a Shinobi like you,
renowned as a Sannin, is not...
then who is?
If you want a Sannin,
there is one more left...
That Tsunade.
Certainly that child probably
has that capability, but...
However, no one knows where she is.
I'll find and bring her back.
If I do that there's no problem, right?
But...
A wise one like Tsunade is meant to
be Hokage more than I, with no motivation.
What do you want to do?
All right.
We'll give it urgent consideration.
However, we'll have three members
from ANBU Black Ops to accompany you
as the search unit for Tsunade.
Don't worry, I won't escape from this.
The guards are not necessary.
However...
There is one guy that I want
to take with me on my trip.
I've found an interesting egg...
What? That is absolutely strange.
Sorry, but if you don't have a ticket,
there's no ramen.
No, wait a minute!
I absolutely had one more.
Huh?
The one that I gave Konohamaru,
was it the last?
Welcome!
Hey, my ramen!
"Make-Out Paradise"
Yo, you two!
You seem to be getting along well.
Fool, Anko asked me to
buy rice dumplings. That's all.
What are you doing here?
While I'm here to buy offerings,
I've made plans to meet here...
with Sasuke.
Huh, it's rare that you wait for people.
Is the offering to Obito?
Obito?
Well... that's about right.
Kakashi, it's strange for
you to be here first.
Well... once in a while.
I don't do natto
and sweet things.
Oh... Is that so?
What?!
This is absolutely positively strange!
You guys aren't from the village...
Why in the world did you come?
I haven't seen you for
a while Asuma-san, Kurenai-san.
If you know about us,
are you former Leaf Shinobi?
— Huh?!
Y-You are?!
Humph, without a doubt...
Uchiha...
Itachi.
You are acquaintances of Itachi-san?
If so...
I'll introduce myself as well.
I'm Hoshigaki Kisame.
Hereafter, I hope to be familiar with you.
Never mind later,
I'm going to beat you now!
Itachi-san...
It seems you're pretty unpopular
in the village too.
I know you, too.
Hoshigake Kisame,
originally a Shinobi
of Hidden Village in the Mist.
Suspected of national covert activities
and of killing a feudal lord,
a Rogue Ninja from Land of Water,
on the wanted list in all nations.
You're a major S-rank criminal
listed in the Bingo Book.
Itachi, you have some nerve
coming back to this village
after causing that awful incident.
Asuma-san... Kurenai-san...
Don't interfere with me.
I don't intend to kill you.
That's not a line for you,
who killed your comrades.
I know there's no way
you'd come here
without any clear purpose
in those suspicious appearance.
What are you after?
This guy is pretty annoying.
Should we kill him?
It doesn't look like we are able
to leave the village so smoothly...
But don't overdo it,
your techniques tend to stand out.
They're done for then.
This is...
Genjutsu.
Pressing down with the tip of his sword...
What strength.
My large sword, Shark Skin...
doesn't cut, but lops it off!
Kurenai... You're late.
With this...
it's over!
Genjutsu of that level doesn't work on me.
This is... Genjutsu Reversal?
Kurenai!
There's no time to look away.
That's what's expected from you, Kurenai-san.
But...
"But" this is as far as it goes...
for you.
What?!
Water Style!
— Water Shark Bomb Jutsu!
The same Jutsu as me?!
Why have you shown up too?
Well... I asked you to take care
of them earlier.
But I kinda felt uneasy, you know.
Shadow clones.
Hatake...
Kakashi.
Jeez... So much fuss for nothing.
I...
I put it under my headband
in order not to drop the important ticket
during morning training.
Okay, that's fine...
Eat well and do your best.
Hmm?
You're going to do it again
after this, right? Training?
Of course! I'm full of motivation.
Good! Here you go.
Another serving for free! Go for it!
Thank you, sir!
Welcome.
Just like I heard...
I had to come and see it.
It seems that you really
are just eating ramen.
Oh, Pervy Sage!
gaman no renzoku dattaro
a cycle of hardship, right?
kokoro de naiteita ndarou
inside, we were crying, right?
jibun de kimeta sono yume dake wa yuzurenai ndarou
but the one thing we won't give up is the dream we've chosen, right?
wakiyaku dakedo
it's a secondary role
kage no hito dakedo
a role in the shadows
yume to mukiau toki kurai
but in reaching for that dream
man naka ni isasete shoujiki ni isasete
let us stay centered, let us stay true
ima made nandomo nan toka akiramezu ni
over and over, we hung on without giving up
ima made nandomo tachi agatte kita janai ka
over and over, we kept coming back up
ima made nandomo
over and over, we believed and dreamed
bokura
nandomo
shinjite
yume mite nandomo
ima made nandomo baka o mite kita janai ka
over and over, we've seen fools
ima made nandomo hito no kage ni tatte kita janai ka
over and over, we've stood in the shadows of others
saa shuyaku da yo jibun no yume kurai wagamama de isasete
now, it's our turn... let us bask in our dreams
Uchiha Itachi...
who became a leader of
ANBU Black Ops at the age of thirteen
and who destroyed
the Uchiha clan single-handedly.
I don't know why he has
suddenly appeared after all this time...
But I don't think we will
allow him to leave so easily.
What is your purpose?!
Next time:
"Sharingan vs Sharingan!!"